http://www.datrondynamics.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy | CNC Machines | DATRON Dynamics, Inc.
LinkedIn
YouTube CNC Tools ShopMy AccountAccount OverviewOrdersShop for ToolsSingle Flute End MillsDouble Flute End MillsTriple Flute End MillsFace MillsBallnose End MillsDrillsEngraversSpecialty End MillsThread MillsCountersink / Chamfer MillsExternal Radius MillsAccessories $0.00 0 Items
ApplicationsHigh-Speed MachiningRapid PrototypingEngravingIndustriesAerospace and DefenseIndustrial ManufacturingConsumer & Industrial ElectronicsJob ShopsMedical DevicesProductsCNC Milling MachinesDATRON neoM8CubeMLCubeM10 ProMXCubeUsed MachinesC5CNC Tools & Accessoriesnext SoftwareCNC ToolsDATRON Machine AccessoriesAutomationORDER TOOLSAboutMeet the Leadership TeamOur CustomersTestimonialsLocationsResourcesBlogCase StudiesWhite PapersNews & EventsPress ReleasesTrade Shows & EventsDATRON Digital Experience DaysContactRequest a Site VisitService & SupportRequest a Quote
Select Page
DATRON Privacy PolicyPrivacy Policy Effective date: May 02, 2018DATRON Dynamics, Inc. (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the https://www.datron.com/ website (the “Service”).This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data.We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible from https://www.datron.com/DefinitionsPersonal Data Personal Data means data about a living individual who can be identified from those data (or from those and other information either in our possession or likely to come into our possession).Usage Data Usage Data is data collected automatically either generated by the use of the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).Cookies Cookies are small pieces of data stored on a User’s device.Data Controller Data Controller means a person who (either alone or jointly or in common with other persons) determines the purposes for which and the manner in which any personal data are, or are to be, processed.For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, we are a Data Controller of your data.Data Processor (or Service Providers) Data Processor (or Service Provider) means any person (other than an employee of the Data Controller) who processes the data on behalf of the Data Controller.We may use the services of various Service Providers in order to process your data more effectively.Data Subject Data Subject is any living individual who is the subject of Personal Data.User The User is the individual using our Service. The User corresponds to the Data Subject, who is the subject of Personal Data.Information Collection And UseWe collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you.Types of Data CollectedPersonal Data While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Data”). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:Email addressFirst name and last namePhone numberAddress, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, CityCookies and Usage DataWe may use your Personal Data to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send.Usage Data We may also collect information how the Service is accessed and used (“Usage Data”). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.Location Data We may use and store information about your location if you give us permission to do so (“Location Data”). We use this data to provide features of our Service, to improve and customize our Service. You can enable or disable location services when you use our Service at any time, through your device settings.Tracking Cookies Data We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information.Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service. Examples of Cookies we use:Session Cookies. We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.Preference Cookies. We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.Security Cookies. We use Security Cookies for security purposes.Use of DataDATRON Dynamics, Inc. uses the collected data for various purposes:To provide and maintain our ServiceTo notify you about changes to our ServiceTo allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do soTo provide customer supportTo gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our ServiceTo monitor the usage of our ServiceTo detect, prevent and address technical issuesTo provide you with news, special offers and general information about other goods, services and events which we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about unless you have opted not to receive such informationRetention of DataDATRON Dynamics, Inc. will retain your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies.DATRON Dynamics, Inc. will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of our Service, or we are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods.Transfer Of DataYour information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to United States and process it there. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.DATRON Dynamics, Inc. will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.Disclosure Of DataBusiness Transaction If DATRON Dynamics, Inc. is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, your Personal Data may be transferred. We will provide notice before your Personal Data is transferred and becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy.Disclosure for Law Enforcement Under certain circumstances, DATRON Dynamics, Inc. may be required to disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency).Legal Requirements DATRON Dynamics, Inc. may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:To comply with a legal obligationTo protect and defend the rights or property of DATRON Dynamics, Inc.To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the ServiceTo protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the publicTo protect against legal liabilitySecurity Of DataThe security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.“Do Not Track” SignalsWe do not support Do Not Track (“DNT”). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked.You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser.Your RightsDATRON Dynamics, Inc. aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data.Whenever made possible, you can update your Personal Data directly within your account settings section. If you are unable to change your Personal Data, please contact us to make the required changes.If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us.In certain circumstances, you have the right:To access and receive a copy of the Personal Data we hold about youTo rectify any Personal Data held about you that is inaccurateTo request the deletion of Personal Data held about youYou have the right to data portability for the information you provide to DATRON Dynamics, Inc.. You can request to obtain a copy of your Personal Data in a commonly used electronic format so that you can manage and move it.Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests.Service ProvidersWe may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service (“Service Providers”), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.Analytics We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service.Google Analytics Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity.For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy Terms web page: http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/Behavioral Remarketing DATRON Dynamics, Inc. uses remarketing services to advertise on third party websites to you after you visited our Service. We and our third-party vendors use cookies to inform, optimize and serve ads based on your past visits to our Service.Google AdWords Google AdWords remarketing service is provided by Google Inc.You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize the Google Display Network ads by visiting the Google Ads Settings page: http://www.google.com/settings/adsGoogle also recommends installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on – https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout – for your web browser. Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on provides visitors with the ability to prevent their data from being collected and used by Google Analytics.For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy Terms web page: http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/Facebook Facebook remarketing service is provided by Facebook Inc. You can learn more about interest-based advertising from Facebook by visiting this page: https://www.facebook.com/help/164968693837950To opt-out from Facebook’s interest-based ads follow these instructions from Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217Facebook adheres to the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising established by the Digital Advertising Alliance. You can also opt-out from Facebook and other participating companies through the Digital Advertising Alliance in the USA http://www.aboutads.info/choices/, the Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada in Canada http://youradchoices.ca/ or the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance in Europe http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/, or opt-out using your mobile device settings.For more information on the privacy practices of Facebook, please visit Facebook’s Data Policy: https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanationLinks To Other SitesOur Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.Children’s PrivacyOur Service does not address anyone under the age of 13 (“Children”).We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.Changes To This Privacy PolicyWe may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the “effective date” at the top of this Privacy Policy.You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.Contact UsIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:By email: info@datron.comBy visiting this page on our website: https://www.datron.com/contact-usBy phone number: 888.262.2833By mail: Datron Dynamics, Inc., 115 Emerson Road, Milford, NH 03055Questions About DATRON CNC Milling Machines?DATRON machines dramatically reduce practically every aspect of your machining workflow. If you have any questions regarding DATRON CNC Milling Machines, tooling, accessories, or more, please contact us.  Contact UsRecent Posts 5 Things You Didn’t Know About the M8Cube Breaking the CNC Machining Bottleneck 9 Things You Need to Know About Vacuum Chucks A Race Car in a World of Tractor Trailers Turning a Garage Into a Factory: Manufacturing RF Waveguides at HomeDATRON Twitter FeedDatron Dynamics@DatronCNC·1hCurrent industry trends show more companies are determined to bring prototyping in-house to optimize workflows and protect IP. Learn why it may be time to invest in bringing prototyping in-house with our new eBook 'Making Things'
created with @autodesk. https://prototypinginhouse.datron.com/Reply on Twitter 1314304675030724608Retweet on Twitter 13143046750307246081Like on Twitter 1314304675030724608Twitter 1314304675030724608Datron Dynamics@DatronCNC·7 Oct“This stuff might fall into the “no quote” pile for a lot of shops because it’s complex, it’s all 3D work, tight tolerances, low quantities, stuff that most people don’t want to touch” - Tim Allard, Rapid DTM. https://bit.ly/3dbRid9
#cnc #aerospace #datron #datroncnc #m8cubeReply on Twitter 1313949225265385474Retweet on Twitter 1313949225265385474Like on Twitter 13139492252653854741Twitter 1313949225265385474Datron Dynamics@DatronCNC·7 OctIn Aerospace and Defense, parts need to be produced right the first time. Few understand this better than Tim Allard of Rapid DTM. After working for large manufacturing companies, Tim decided to start his own business focusing on quality over quantity. https://bit.ly/2D7zCjbReply on Twitter 1313876810212478977Retweet on Twitter 13138768102124789771Like on Twitter 1313876810212478977Twitter 1313876810212478977Datron Dynamics@DatronCNC·6 OctIt's Tooling Tuesday featuring a Stepped Single Flue End Mill. For wide-open shallow pockets, we combined the Stepped Single Flute with a wide stepover and a smaller depth of cut as full-depth trochoidal toolpaths were not the most efficient strategy. https://bit.ly/2Sz914VReply on Twitter 1313510197030260738Retweet on Twitter 1313510197030260738Like on Twitter 13135101970302607381Twitter 1313510197030260738Datron Dynamics@DatronCNC·5 OctThe correct answer to our Did You Know - CNC Milling Trivia is... an aluminum ashtray. After the CNC press conference, The Air Force signed contracted MIT’s Electronic Systems Laboratory for a “Computer-Aided Design Project”, resulting in the Automated Engineering Design (AED).2Reply on Twitter 1313136772281442306Retweet on Twitter 1313136772281442306Like on Twitter 1313136772281442306Twitter 1313136772281442306Datron Dynamics@DatronCNC·2 OctWhat's important to you when shopping for a new CNC Mill? A high RPM spindle? Large work envelope? For Ed Kramer, placing a machine in his garage meant that he needed a very capable machine with a small footprint. Find out what he selected: https://bit.ly/3ipiq9x
#datron #cncReply on Twitter 1312061336801751041Retweet on Twitter 1312061336801751041Like on Twitter 13120613368017510411Twitter 1312061336801751041Datron Dynamics@DatronCNC·30 SepWhen should you use a drill as opposed to an end mill? If you're milling a bunch of small holes like we are in this 17-4 steel plate, drilling is way to go. However, large holes or a variety of holes, would be better suited for an end mill. Learn more: https://bit.ly/2OKpz8tReply on Twitter 1311352438885167104Retweet on Twitter 13113524388851671041Like on Twitter 13113524388851671041Twitter 1311352438885167104Datron Dynamics@DatronCNC·28 SepDo your machines mill only aluminum? No! Although DATRONs rip through aluminum, they're also great for milling brass, acrylic, delrin, stainless steel, and more.
Material - UHMW Speed & Feed - 25k RPM, 473"/min Tool - 4 in 1 Single Flute End Mill
https://bit.ly/344XHTnReply on Twitter 1310591637555499008Retweet on Twitter 1310591637555499008Like on Twitter 1310591637555499008Twitter 1310591637555499008Datron Dynamics@DatronCNC·25 SepDid you know that we also manufacture our own cutting tools? Ground from micro-grain carbide, DATRON tools feature polished edges that provide longer life, burr-free machining, and superior finishes. See how our tools are made check out the new tool store. https://bit.ly/2ZpSLquReply on Twitter 1309511890599645184Retweet on Twitter 1309511890599645184Like on Twitter 13095118905996451842Twitter 1309511890599645184Datron Dynamics@DatronCNC·24 SepTeam Valkyrie is heading out on the road today to compete in the upcoming @battlebots season. We had the pleasure of making some generative designed frame rails and other parts for their BattleBot and can't wait to see Valkyrie take on the competition! LET THE SPARKS FLY!4Reply on Twitter 1309193190717751296Retweet on Twitter 1309193190717751296Like on Twitter 1309193190717751296Twitter 1309193190717751296Load More...Contact UsDATRON Dynamics, Inc. North American Headquarters115 Emerson Road Milford, NH 03055 Tel: 603.215.5850Toll Free: 888.262.2833Fax: 603.672.8067Privacy Policy Terms & Conditions
Facebook
Twitter
LinkedIn
YouTube © Copyright 2020. DATRON Dynamics, Inc.. All Rights Reserved.
We use cookies to ensure we give you the best experience on our website. You can update your cookie settings at any time. Read More ACCEPTPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close Privacy OverviewThis website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Necessary Always EnabledNecessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessaryAny cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
Share This
Facebook
Twitter
LinkedIn
Shopping CartThere are no products in the cart!Continue Shopping
